awardspace.info 2010-06-12

# Privacy Policy | AwardSpace.com

Privacy Policy

  1. **Statement**

AWARDSPACE.COM has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate commitment to customer privacy. The following discloses the information gathering practices for AWARDSPACE.COM.

  2. **Automatically Logged Information**

We use your IP address to help identify visitors and to help improve the website's performance for different browser/operating system configurations.

  3. **Email Communication**

We will not intentionally monitor or disclose any of your e-mail messages unless we believe or we are required to do so:  
\- To enforce these Terms and Conditions,  
\- By law,  
\- To defend our corporation in any action,   
\- To protect our property, dignity and innocence.

AWARDSPACE.COM will not send to its customers any unsolicited information, including e-mails, except as mentioned below. New Customers will receive a AWARDSPACE.COM welcome e-mail providing the user credentials and explaining the features provided by the service. AWARDSPACE.COM may also send periodic member letters to announce important service changes, new features, technical issue updates and news about the Service.

  4. **Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to identify you each time you visit our site. We also use cookies for web site statistics. These statistics consist of browser and operating system types, search engine keywords, referrer IDs, how long a visitor stays at the site, and pages viewed at our site. In no way do these statistics track users after they leave AWARDSPACE.COM.

  5. **Advertisers**

Your personal information will never be sold or traded for any reason. You agree to respect the privacy and confidentiality of others. Since privacy is a function of your password, we encourage you to change your password frequently and not share it with anyone.

  6. **Registration Forms**

Contact information from the registration forms is used to contact the customer when necessary.

  7. **External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. AWARDSPACE.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

  8. **Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

  9. **Children Guidelines**

We care deeply about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:  
We will NOT collect, use, or distribute personally identifiable information to third parties without prior verifiable parental consent.  
We will NOT grant children access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that could give the them the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

  10. **News Letter Notification Policy**

Customers may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or notices from AWARDSPACE.COM by following simple procedure available with a link at the botton of the newsletter email.

Please note, however, that AWARDSPACE.COM reserves the right to send bulletins and other important information regarding our services at our discretion.

  11. **Changes to our privacy policy**

We at AWARDSPACE.COM reserve the rights to change our privacy policy at any time without notice.
